Raging wind, while your visage fades away
当你面容枯萎 飓风大作
Where the world lies in pieces at my feet
这便是在我脚下粉碎的世界
The fire and the storm and the snow and the mist
烈火与风暴，降雪与迷雾
Struggle inside, help me gain insight
忍痛于怀，辅我知觉
Hail my proud queen, on and on on and on
女王万岁 不绝于耳
That wax and wane showed its ebb and flow
阴晴圆缺有其涨落
Selah, selah, are chanting evermore
休止声声无休无止
Hear, oh hear all the voices trapped in thee
侧耳倾听汝之心声
See myself in your eyes that's colorless
在你的失色的瞳仁中我看见自己
Visions pass and emotions run through me
幻觉过后我的情感倾泻而出
Struggle inside, helped me gain insight
忍痛于怀，辅我知觉
Hail my proud queen, on and on on and on
女王万岁 不绝于耳
That wax and wane showed its ebb and flow
阴晴圆缺有其涨落
Selah, selah, are chanting evermore
休止声声无休无止
Hear, oh hear all the voices trapped in thee
侧耳倾听汝之心声
Fair moonlight, will you fill my void eyes?
公义之月，你会盈满我空洞的目光吗？
Hail my proud queen on and on
女王万岁 不绝于耳
Selah selah are chanting evermore
休止声声无休无止
Hear, oh hear all the voices trapped in thee
侧耳倾听汝之心声